<Defs>
	
	<!-- T1 Fabrication -->
	
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_ImperiumTechBase">
		<defName>GW_MilitariumFabrication</defName>
		<label>militarium fabrication</label>
		<description>The Tactica Imperium is the cornerstone of Imperial military strategy in GrimWorld 40,000. It's a weathered tome filled with battle wisdom, guiding commanders through the complexities of warfare. With its doctrines on combined arms and adaptable tactics, it shapes the minds of Imperial leaders, aiding them in their quest for survival and dominance.</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>MultiAnalyzer</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<baseCost>1000</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>0.50</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>2.70</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<!-- Vehicle -->
	
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_ImperiumTechBase">
		<defName>GW_VehiclesFabrication</defName>
		<label>vehicles fabrication</label>
		<description>. . .</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>GW_MilitariumFabrication</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<baseCost>1000</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>2.50</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>6.00</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_ImperiumTechBase">
		<defName>GW_ImperialTransport</defName>
		<label>imperial transport</label>
		<description>. . .</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>GW_VehiclesFabrication</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<baseCost>1000</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>3.50</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>5.50</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_ImperiumTechBase">
		<defName>GW_ImperialBike</defName>
		<label>imperial bike</label>
		<description>. . .</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>GW_VehiclesFabrication</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<baseCost>1000</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>3.50</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>6.00</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<!-- Weapon -->
	
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_ImperiumTechBase">
		<defName>GW_MilitariumBasicMelee</defName>
		<label>Basic melee weapons</label>
		<description>The chainsword is essentially a sword with powered teeth that run along a single-edged blade like that of a chainsaw. Most versions of the weapon make use of monomolecularly-edged or otherwise razor-sharp teeth. Chainswords are not subtle weapons, and wielding one is a statement in its own right: they are horrific tools of war, designed to bite, tear and eviscerate where more primitive blades merely cut and slice.</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>Machining</li>
			<li>LongBlades</li>
			<li>GW_MilitariumFabrication</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<baseCost>3500</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>1.50</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>3.80</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_ImperiumTechBase">
		<defName>GW_Autoguns</defName>
		<label>autoguns</label>
		<description>An Autogun is a fully automatic Auto Weapon that fires solid-slug ballistic rounds at the intended target in rapid succession. Cheap, rugged and reliable, it can be found throughout the Imperium of Man, where it is appreciated for its decent damage and accuracy. Its main drawbacks are its weight and the need to carry a large amount of cumbersome ammunition for prolonged operations. The latter drawback has led to the Astra Militarum being equipped with Lasguns as its standard armament since the early 32nd Millennium.</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>Gunsmithing</li>
			<li>GW_MilitariumFabrication</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<baseCost>1600</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>1.50</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>4.30</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_ImperiumTechBase">
		<defName>GW_Launchers</defName>
		<label>launchers</label>
		<description>A Grenade Launcher serves the role of an explosives launcher weapon for the Imperial armed forces that can be used and carried by a single, un-augmented Human. The grenades are typically equipped with either Frag or Krak explosive charges, although Grenade Launcher projectile warheads are smaller and less powerful than their Missile Launcher warhead equivalents.</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>Gunsmithing</li>
			<li>GW_MilitariumFabrication</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<baseCost>3500</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>1.50</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>5.50</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<!-- Armor -->
	
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_ImperiumTechBase">
		<defName>GW_MilitariumArmor</defName>
		<label>militarium armor</label>
		<description>In GrimWorld 40,000, Militarum Armor is sturdy protection for Imperial Guard soldiers, made from reinforced ceramite. Marked with the Aquila and regimental insignias, it symbolizes duty and sacrifice. Equipped for hazardous conditions, it stands as a defense against the darkness.</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>GW_MilitariumFabrication</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<baseCost>1500</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>1.50</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>2.00</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_ImperiumTechBase">
		<defName>GW_RatlingArmor</defName>
		<label>ratling armor</label>
		<description>Ratlings, small abhumans employed as snipers by the Imperium of Man, are granted Imperial citizenship despite their mutant status. They excel as marksmen, capable of precise shots from over a kilometer away. In battle, Ratlings can exact a heavy toll on enemy forces, using their knack for staying out of harm's way to their advantage.</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>GW_MilitariumArmor</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<baseCost>1500</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>3.50</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>1.50</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_ImperiumTechBase">
		<defName>GW_OgrynArmor</defName>
		<label>ogryn armor</label>
		<description>The Ogryn, massive abhumans employed as shock troopers by the Imperium of Man, are physically powerful mutants standing around 10 feet tall. They hail from cold, barren planets with high gravity, making them larger and bulkier than humans. Despite limited intellect, they compensate with overwhelming physical strength and loyalty, making them exceptional shock troops for direct assaults on the front lines of battle in the Astra Militarum's Militarum Auxilla.</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>GW_MilitariumArmor</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<baseCost>1500</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>3.50</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>1.90</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_ImperiumTechBase">
		<defName>GW_VostoyanFirstborn</defName>
		<label>vostoyan firstborn</label>
		<description>The Vostroyan Firstborn in Warhammer 40,000 are a distinguished regiment from the hive world of Vostroya. Adorned in elaborate carapace armor, they excel in marksmanship and methodical tactics. Armed with lasguns and ornate weaponry, they bring lethal firepower to battle. Each soldier embodies the regiment's heritage and commitment to excellence, showcasing the Imperium's capacity to produce specialized forces for the challenges of the 41st millennium.</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>GW_MilitariumArmor</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<baseCost>1500</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>4.50</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>1.10</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_ImperiumTechBase">
		<defName>GW_MilitarumBackpack</defName>
		<label>militarum backpack</label>
		<description>. . .</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>GW_MilitariumArmor</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<baseCost>1500</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>2.50</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>1.50</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_ImperiumTechBase">
		<defName>GW_ArmaggedonSteelLegion</defName>
		<label>armaggedon steel legion</label>
		<description>The Armageddon Steel Legion in Warhammer 40,000 is a disciplined regiment from the industrial world of Armageddon. Clad in gas masks and flak armor, they excel in urban warfare and combined arms tactics. Armed with lasguns and supported by armored vehicles, they reclaim urban territories effectively. Each soldier embodies resilience and adaptability, defending their homeworld and the Imperium in the grim darkness of the 41st millennium.</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>GW_MilitariumArmor</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<baseCost>1500</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>4.50</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>1.90</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_ImperiumTechBase">
		<defName>GW_OfficerOfAstraMilitarum</defName>
		<label>officer of astra militarum</label>
		<description>Officers of the Militarum in Warhammer 40,000 have distinct attire: the Commissar wears a black greatcoat and peaked cap, the Militarum Priest dons religious robes, Militarum Engineseer which help Guard with thier tanks, the Field Medic dresses in standard fatigues with a red cross symbol, and the Sanctioned Psyker is clad in robes with psychic glyphs, bearing a glowing mark, and wielding a crackling staff.</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>GW_MilitariumArmor</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<baseCost>1500</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>2.50</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>0.80</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_ImperiumTechBase">
		<defName>GW_CatachanJungle</defName>
		<label>catachan jungle</label>
		<description>The Catachan Jungle Fighters of Warhammer 40,000 are elite soldiers bred on the death world Catachan. Known for their combat skills and resilience, they wear camouflaged fatigues for jungle warfare. Masters of guerrilla tactics, they ambush enemies with precision. Armed with rugged weaponry, they turn the jungle into a deadly weapon. Their reputation for skill and tenacity is legendary in the Imperium, symbolizing the ability to thrive in hazardous conditions.</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>GW_MilitariumArmor</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<baseCost>1500</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>3.50</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>1.10</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_ImperiumTechBase">
		<defName>GW_TallarnDesertRaider</defName>
		<label>tallarn desert raider</label>
		<description>The Tallarn Desert Raiders in Warhammer 40,000 are known for their swift and adaptive warfare. Hailing from Tallarn, they excel in desert combat with their mobility and hit-and-run tactics. Clad in desert camouflage, they blend into their surroundings. Armed with lasguns and fast-moving vehicles, they bring rapid firepower to battle. Each soldier embodies adaptability and mastery of desert warfare, showcasing the Imperium's ability to produce specialized forces.</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>GW_MilitariumArmor</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<baseCost>1500</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>4.50</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>1.50</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_ImperiumTechBase">
		<defName>GW_DeathKorpsOfKrieg</defName>
		<label>death korps of krieg</label>
		<description>The Death Korps of Krieg in Warhammer 40,000 are disciplined soldiers from the irradiated Death World of Krieg. They wear gas masks and trench coats, reflecting their harsh environment. Known for discipline and resilience, they excel in trench warfare and sieges. Armed with lasguns and heavy artillery, they employ attrition tactics on the battlefield. Each soldier carries the weight of their world's tragic history, exemplifying the resolve needed to defend humanity.</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>GW_MilitariumArmor</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<baseCost>1500</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>4.50</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>0.30</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_ImperiumTechBase">
		<defName>GW_ValhallanIceWarrior</defName>
		<label>valhallan ice warrior</label>
		<description>The Valhallan Ice Warriors in Warhammer 40,000 are stalwart defenders from the frozen world of Valhalla. Cloaked in winter gear, they excel in enduring extreme cold and expert marksmanship. Armed with lasguns and heavy weapons, they bring potent firepower to battle. Each soldier embodies resilience and adaptability, showcasing the Imperium's capacity to produce specialized forces for the harsh realities of the 41st millennium.</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>GW_MilitariumArmor</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<baseCost>1500</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>3.50</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>0.70</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_ImperiumTechBase">
		<defName>GW_ElysianDropTroops</defName>
		<label>elysian drop troops</label>
		<description>. . .</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>GW_MilitariumArmor</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<baseCost>1500</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>2.50</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>0.30</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_ImperiumTechBase">
		<defName>GW_MordianIronGuard</defName>
		<label>mordian iron guard</label>
		<description>The Mordian Iron Guard in Warhammer 40,000 is a disciplined regiment from the fortress world of Mordian. They wear distinctive uniforms and excel in line formations and defensive tactics. Armed with lasguns and heavy weapons, they bring disciplined firepower to battle. Each soldier embodies precision and order, dedicated to defending the Imperium.</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>GW_MilitariumArmor</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<baseCost>1500</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>4.50</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>0.70</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_ImperiumTechBase">
		<defName>GW_TanithFirstAndOnly</defName>
		<label>tarnith first and only</label>
		<description>. . .</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>GW_MilitariumArmor</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<baseCost>1500</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>3.50</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>0.30</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<!-- Material -->
	
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_ImperiumTechBase">
		<defName>GW_GrimworldMaterials</defName>
		<label>imperium materials</label>
		<description>Allows for the creation of materials like rockcrete and plascrete. Furnace allow to produce them.</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>GW_MilitariumFabrication</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<baseCost>2000</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>1.50</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>0.90</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_ImperiumTechBase">
		<defName>GW_AdvancedGrimworldMaterials</defName>
		<label>advanced grimworld materials</label>
		<description>Allows for the creation of advanced materials, like relic components.</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>Fabrication</li>
			<li>GW_GrimworldMaterials</li>
			<li>AdvancedFabrication</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<baseCost>3500</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>1.50</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>0.30</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<!-- Drug -->
	
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_ImperiumTechBase">
		<defName>GW_DrugProduction</defName>
		<label>imperium drug production</label>
		<description>Allows for the production of various mind altering substances common throughout the imperium, from fenrisian ale to combat stims. Fenrisian Ale, called Mjød in the unique Fenrisian Low Gothic dialect, is an extremely potent concoction distilled from the fermentation of the native plants of Fenris. Battle stimulants basicly works as massive power boost, but have cost of addiction.</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>GW_MilitariumFabrication</li>
			<li>DrugProduction</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<baseCost>2000</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>1.50</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>4.80</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<!-- Turret -->
	
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_ImperiumTechBase">
		<defName>GW_ImperiumDefenseStructure</defName>
		<label>imperium defense structure</label>
		<description>Imperium Defense in GrimWorld 40,000 is a robust network of fortifications showcasing the Imperium's resolve against threats. It includes walls, automated defenses, and strategic positions. Scarred bunkers symbolize defenders' commitment, embodying the Imperium's determination to survive.</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>GW_MilitariumFabrication</li>
			<li>GasOperation</li>
			<li>GunTurrets</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<baseCost>2000</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>2.50</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>3.80</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

</Defs>